optimumnutrition.com 2019-06-22

# Privacy Policy | Optimum Nutrition

This is the privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") for Optimumnutrition.com ("Site", "we", "us," or "our"), an Internet website offered by Optimum Nutrition, Inc. This Privacy Policy applies whether you are accessing the Site via a personal computer, mobile device or any other technology or devices now known or hereafter developed or discovered. Your privacy is important to us. Please take a moment to familiarize yourself with our privacy practices. We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time by updating this page, so please check this page periodically to ensure that you are informed about any changes that we implement. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, please do not participate in the Site or any features, activities or services offered though the Site.

#### COLLECTION AND USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

Personal information is data that can be used to uniquely identify or contact a single person. You may be asked to provide your personal information any time you are in contact with us or our affiliates. We may share this personal information with our affiliates and use it consistent with this Privacy Policy.

Here are some examples of how we collect personal information:

  * When you purchase products through the Site, you are required to provide certain information, such as your first and last name, address, telephone, and email address.
  * If you choose to communicate with us through email, via our website, by telephone, in writing or through other means, we may collect any personal information that you voluntarily provide to us.
  * There may be a separate registration process to enter promotions such as contests and sweepstakes that may require the submission of all or some of the following: your first and last name, address, telephone number and date of birth. Additional information may be requested depending on the specific promotion, but submission of such information may be optional. The promotion's entry page or rules will provide the specific requirements.

Here are some examples of how we use personal information:

  * The personal information that we collect allows us to keep you posted on our latest product announcements, promotions, special offers, and upcoming events. It also helps us improve our products, services, content, and advertising
  * From time to time, we may use your personal information to send important notices. Because this information is important to your interaction with us, you may not opt out of receiving these communications
  * We also may use personal information for internal purposes such as audits, data analysis, and research to improve our products, services, and customer communications.
  * If you enter a sweepstake, contest, or similar promotion, we may use the information that you provide to administer those programs.

#### COLLECTION AND USE OF NON-PERSONAL INFORMATION

Non-personal information is data in a form that does not permit direct association with any specific individual. As is true of most websites, we may collect, use, and disclose non-personal information, such as user Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type and language, Internet Service Provider (ISP), referring and exit pages, and date/time stamp, for any purpose, such as to better understand user behavior and facilitate the effectiveness of our content and advertising.

#### DISCLOSURE TO THIRD PARTIES

At times, we may make certain personal information available to strategic partners that work with us to provide products and services, or that help us market to customers. Personal information will only be shared by us to provide or improve our products, services and advertising; it will not be shared with third parties for their marketing purposes.

We also may disclose any information that we possess about you (including your identity) if we determine that such disclosure is necessary in connection with any investigation or complaint regarding your use of the Site, or to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our rights or property, or the rights or property of visitors to or users of the Site, including our customers. We reserve the right at all times to disclose any information that we deem necessary to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request. We also may disclose your information when we determine that applicable law requires or permits such disclosure, including exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection purposes, or if we determine that disclosure is reasonably necessary to enforce our Terms of Use. Additionally, in the event that we undergo a corporate reorganization, merger, or sale, we may transfer any and all personal information that we collect to any third party involved in such transaction.

#### COOKIES & DO NOT TRACK REQUESTS

We use cookies and other persistent identifiers to enhance your experience and track information about visitors and visits to our Site. Cookies are small files that enable this Site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and carry certain information. Customer's may have the ability to have their personal computer warn them each time a cookie is set, or turn off cookies through their browser. Each browser is different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. Turning cookies off may interfere with the normal functionality of the site.

In addition, some web browsers may transmit "do-not-track" signals to the websites with which the browser communicates. We currently do not take action in response to these signals.

#### REQUESTS TO OPT-OUT, REMOVE OR MODIFY INFORMATION

If you do not want to be on our electronic mailing list, you can opt out any time. To modify your e-mail subscription, please unsubscribe from emails via the unsubscribe link in each email.

_Last Updated: JUNE 19, 2017_
